NAA Records 5775
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Seward, Ralph T., 1949 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Letter regarding organizational structure of the Academy
- Simkin, William E., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Includes copy of a letter from Simkin to Alfred A. Colby regarding policy for acceptance of applicants to NAA (11/22/50) and routine
- Simkin, William E., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Simkin, William E., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Simkin, William E., 1951 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Routine
- Wolff, David A., 1952 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Letter and attachment from Gabriel N. Alexander to Wolff regarding "Statement of Procedure to be Followed by the Committee on Ethics" (5/23/52) and routine
- Wallen, Saul, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Includes Report of the President, NAA, January 29, by Saul Wallen. 3 pp.
- Platt, Harry H., 1958 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Includes Report and Recommendations of the Special Committee to Consider the Aims and Purposes of the Academy, 3/18/58
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1958 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  Includes "Report of the Special Committee on Membership Status", 12/10/59 - 4 pp. and "Minority Memorandum" to the report, 12/24/59 by William Simkin; includes 3rd draft of a proposed United States Labor Arbitration Act formulated by the NAA Committee on Law and Legislation, Russell A. Smith, Chairman, 11/24/59 - 21 pp.; proposed revision of the constitution and bylaws, 10/13/59; summary of discussion of Michigan Region meeting, 5/5/59, 4 pp.; Report of the Committee on Continuing Cooperation With the Appointing Agencies, 4/59, 21 pp.; "Our Avaricious Arbitrators" by AFL-CIO Industrial Union Department, Winter 1959 which was distributed to and discussed at Regional meetings, and subject of much correspondence.
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  Includes Preliminary Report on Structure, 4/5/60, 13 pp.; letter of resignation signed by W. Willard Wirtz, under Secretary of Labor; letter signed by Governor Edmund Brown (CA)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1960-1961 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Dash, G. Allan, Jr., 1986 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1950-1957 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  Brown's answers to Governor Meyner's (NJ) Committee on Public Utility Labor Legislation, 3/8/54, 3 pp.
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1958 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1960 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1960 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1960 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1960 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1967-1975 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1976 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  Includes discussion and copy of the redefined "Waiver Policy," (waiver of $200 dues for certain members)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Brown, Rev. Leo C., 1978 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Alexander, Gabriel N., 1961 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Aaron, Benjamin, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Aaron, Benjamin, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Aaron, Benjamin, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Aaron, Benjamin, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Aaron, Benjamin, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  Includes Garrett's personal reaction to the Liaison Committee report, 11/1/63; correspondence about two problems referred to Ethics Committee - 1. Should persons who served in any capacity on behalf of companies be members of the Academy. 2. Should arbitrators continue to accept assignments when they are 18 months late in getting out awards, 9/63; letter about officially constituted Committee on the Training of Arbitrators, 4/63 and related routine correspondence; correspondence about whether Chuck Dowd's, Director, Bureau of Mediation for the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania should fill application for membership in NAA, 3/63; correspondence about the Academy establishing a bibliography of member publications
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Garrett, Sylvester, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- Kelliher, Peter M., 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  Includes correspondence about Bill Wirtz talk on excessive fees in arbitration
- Kelliher, Peter M., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  Includes brief discussion by Abraham Stockman about looking into the possibility of incorporating the Academy, 4/16/64; suggestions from Peter Seitz about avoiding disorder at future annual meetings, 2/14/64.
- Kelliher, Peter M., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- Kelliher, Peter M., 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Smith, Russell A., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- Smith, Russell A., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  Includes correspondence about Cy Ching's admission to membership without compliance with procedural pre-requisites specified in By-Laws, 11/65; "Proposal To Establish As A Continuing Institution an `Arbitration Conference' as an Adjunct of the NAA", 2/65, 7 pp.
- Smith, Russell A., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 67)
- Smith, Russell A., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Smith, Russell A., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Smith, Russell A., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- Smith, Russell A., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- Fleming, Robben W., 1964 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Fleming, Robben W., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Fleming, Robben W., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  Includes a copy of resignation intent of David P. Miller as Secretary, 7/26/66
- Fleming, Robben W., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 75)
- Fleming, Robben W., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 76)
- Fleming, Robben W., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 77)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  Includes discussion of annual meeting "Guest Policy"
- Luskin, Bert L., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 79)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 80)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 81)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 82)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  Includes reactions to the UAW's action in termination the Ford-UAW Umpire (7/10/67), Harry H. Platt; correspondence about issuance of special "charter member" certificates, 6/67 and routine
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 84)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 85)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 86)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 87)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 88)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 89)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 90)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 91)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 92)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 93)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 94)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967 (Box 13, Folder 95)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1968 (Box 13, Folder 96)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 97)
- Luskin, Bert L, 1947-1963 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Includes membership lists, committee lists and routine correspondence
- Luskin, Bert L., 1964 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Correspondence re. Pearce Davis nomination for Vice President and routine
- Luskin, Bert L., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Includes rosters, correspondence nominating Luskin for President-elect and routine
- Luskin, Bert L., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Includes correspondence about charter members
- Luskin, Bert L., 1967-1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Correspondence about charter members
- Luskin, Bert L., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Killingsworth, Charles C., 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Killingsworth, Charles C., 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Killingsworth, Charles C., 1967-1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Hill, James C., 1968 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Includes memo regarding organizing of Atlanta Hotel Workers and NLRB findings on the subject; Routine
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Includes discussion of the establishment of the Adam Horvitz Memorial Collection on peaceful resolutions of conflicts at Friends World College; Discussion of choosing of International Correspondents(overseas neutrals in labor-management disputes)
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Includes description of International Correspondent responsibilities; Report On Proposal of NAA Relationships With Overseas Neutrals, 2p.; Routine
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Includes original of agreement with Friends World College regarding the disposition of the Aaron Horvitz Memorial Fund; Routine
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Includes discussion of the new Special Committee of the National Academy of Arbitrators on Disputes Settlement in Public Employment; Routine
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  Includes NAA-Cornell Conference material (The Industrial and Labor Relations Report, Spring 1968); The report on the Milwaukee Technical College Negotiations; Routine
- Hill, James C., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  Includes report of the NAA Committee on the Training of New Arbitrators (January, 1968), 4p.; Routine
- Hill, James C., 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  Includes article by Marcia L. Greenbaum - Saul Wallen: A Lifetime Commitment to Problem Solving, 19p.; Routine
- Hill, James C., 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Hill, James C., 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Hill, James C., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Hill, James C., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Hill, James C., 1975 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Hill, James C., 1964-1981 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  Includes Michigan Board decision ordering City of Detroit to implement Agency Shop Clause in Firemen's Pact, 3p.; Routine
- Mckelvey, Jean T., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Lewis, Gill M., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Lewis, Gill M., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Barrett, Gerald A., 1972 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Barrett, Gerald A., 1972 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Rock, Eli, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  Includes NAA list of officers, governors and committee chairmen from 1947; Routine
- Rock, Eli, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Rock, Eli, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  Includes Code of Professional Responsibility for Arbitrators of Labor-Management Disputes, 25p.; Routine
- Rock, Eli, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Rock, Eli, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Miller, David P., 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Miller, David P., 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Miller, David P., 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Miller, David P., 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Miller, David P., 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Valtin, Rolf, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Valtin, Rolf, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Valtin, Rolf, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Valtin, Rolf, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Valtin, Rolf, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Woods, H.D., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Woods, H.D., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Woods, H.D., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Woods, H.D., 1976 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Stark, Arthur, 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Stark, Arthur, 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Stark, Arthur, 1975-1978 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Stark, Arthur, 1975-1979 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  Includes letter from Arthur Stark to Chronicle staff regarding establishment of a Chronicle Staff Committee, 9/8/77; Routine
- Stark, Arthur, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  Includes notice of 12/6/75 in which Board of Governors adopted a resolution to permit Academy members to express committee preferences - 4/16/77; Routine
- Stark, Arthur, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  Includes memorandum regarding the institutionalization of The Chronicle - 10/4/77; Routine
- Stark, Arthur, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  Includes memorandum from Stark regarding the establishment of a Program Resources Committee describing its purposes and functions; Routine
- Stark Arthur, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  Includes letter from chairman of the Committee on Public Employment Disputes Settlements to its members listing their findings and endorsements - 4/25/77
- Stark, Arthur, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  Includes description and purpose of the Committee on Regional Organization; Constitution and By-Laws of the Committee on Regional Organization, 2p.; Routine
- Stark, Arthur, 1977-1979 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  Includes letter from John Keagel to Arthur Stark regarding the findings of the Legal Affairs Committee with respect to the "legal protection" of the individual arbitrator - 5/11/77; Routine
- Stark, Arthur, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Stark, Arthur, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  Includes reports on the current problem dissatisfaction regarding the "Statement of Policy Relative to Membership Standards" - 10/8/79 & 11/1/79; Routine
- Stark, Arthur, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  Includes first Report of Special Committee on
- Stark, Arthur, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  Includes 2 letters from John E. Dunsford and Mark Kahn, attorneys at law expressing strong misgivings about procedural portions of the 12/20/79 Report on Membership Standards; Final Report of Special Committee on Membership Standards to the President, 25 p.; Routine
- Mittehthal, Richard, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  Includes the transcribed Richard Mittenthal/Ralph Seward tapes wherein Mittenthal interviews Seward on 4/14/77, 154 p.
- Mittenthal, Richard, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  Includes 2nd copy of Mittehthal/Seward interview
- Robins, Eva, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- Robins, Eva, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- Robins, Eva, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- McDermott, Clare B., 1980 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- Jones, Edgar, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  Includes Report by Edgar A. Jones and Kathleen Peratis on Arbitration and Federal Rights Under Collective Agreements In 1969, 49p.
- Abernethy, Byron R., 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- Abernethy, Byron R., 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 81)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  Includes 10/12/84 Report from the Auditing Committee to the Board of Governors of NAA on the financial history of NAA since 1971, 7p. 9/6/84 Report from Alex Nelson to Board of Governors on the Formation of a Tax-Exempt Organization, 13p.; Routine
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  Includes Legal Representation Program and Fund Policy Statement Adopted by the Board of Governors, 5/22/84, 3p.; Routine
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Dunsford, John E., 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  Includes mid-year fiscal report submitted on 10/25/84 from Dallas Jones, Secretary Treasurer to the Board of Governors, 5p.; Financial Report for the fiscal 1984 year, submitted 5/31/84, 7p.; Financial Report of 12/31/83 for fiscal year 1983 - 2 copies, 7p.; Routine
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  Includes Report of 9/6/84 from Alex Elson to Board of Governors on the Formation of a Tax-Exempt Organization, 13p.; Report of the Special Committee on the Academy's Role in the Development of New Arbitrators, 13p.; Routine
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  Includes - Report dated 10/1/82 of the NAA Committee on Professional Responsibility and Grievances regarding publication of opinions and awards, 2p.; Routine
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  Includes - NAA Chronicle Committee Report to Board of Governors, 5/1/85, 6p.; Routine
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  Includes - 4/28/84 Report of the Designation Liaison Committee with regard to publication of arbitration opinions, criteria for arbitrator selection, etc.., 4p.; Report of the NAA Intern-Mentor Activities Program, 8p.; Report of the Law and Legislation Committee to 1985 NAA Annual meeting on Supreme Court Decisions, 19p.; Routine
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  Includes Policy Statement of the Legal Representation Program and Fund; Minutes of the Board of Governors Meeting 11/1-2/84, 26p.; Bibliographical sketches of 39 applicants for membership
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  Includes Handbook on Code of Professional Responsibility for Arbitrators of Labor-Management Disputes and correspondence relating to proposed changed to the Code; Report of Committee on Public Employment Disputes Settlement, 13p.; Routine
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  Includes Report on Academy Members' Experience with Tripartite Arbitration in the Early 1980's, 11p.; Financial Report of NAA dated 5/31/84 for preceding 5 month period, 10p.; Routine
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  Includes report on NAA Legal Representation Program 8/6/84; Correspondence and court decisions regarding the subpoena of Joseph Lownberg, arbitrator, to appear before a grand jury; Memorandum of decision of Mass. Superior Court pertaining to the case of Old Rochester Teachers' Club vs. Old Rochester School District et al.; Court proceedings and decision in the case of Kenneth Wood et al. vs. General Teamsters Union regarding the Union's breach of duty which thereby tainted the arbitrator's decision; Correspondence between Robert G. Howlett, arbitrator, and Bill Saxton, attorney, regarding Howlett's refusal to willingly testify in General Teamsters' Union case because of NAA policy, but explains he would have wanted to; Routine
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Dunsford, John E., 1985 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Schedler, Carl R, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Memos and articles about conciliation and arbitration
- Schedler, Carl R, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Schedler, Carl R, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1940 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Correspondence about arbitration work of the Conciliation Service
- Schedler, Carl R., 1940 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Routine arbitration correspondence and about conciliators appointing arbitrators
- Schedler, Carl R., 1940 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1940 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1941 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1947 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Includes report on activities of meeting of local arbitrators in Minnesota area 12/48; Minutes of Membership Committee 9/48; Brief discussions of various regional meetings; Correspondence about George Cheney's membership in NAA 2/48; Correspondence about and copy of a proposed membership application form 2/48
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1948 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1949 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  Includes report of chairman, Committee on Regional Conferences 1/49, 6p.; Correspondence requesting Schedler to become Secretary of The Academy 1/49
- Schedler, Carl R., 1950 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  Includes correspondence between Schedler and A. Langley Coffey about standards governing fees of arbitrators 5/50; An agreement between Ducirco, Inc. and NAA to lease Room 1101, Connecticut Ave. and Dupont Circle for offices beginning 5/1/50 and ending date indicated; Correspondence from David A. Wolff about The Academy presenting an annual award for outstanding contributions to industrial peace or improved labor relations 2/50
- Schedler, Carl R., 1950 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1950 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1951 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  Includes "Statement of Procedure to be Followed by the Committee on Ethics" N.D., 1p.
- Schedler, Carl R., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Schedler, Carl R., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Colby, Alfred A., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  Letter to Dean John Day Larkin includes Colby's opinion of Mr. Dworkin's application
- Alexander, Gabriel N., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Alexander, Gabriel N., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  Includes minutes, Board of Governors meeting 1/23/54, and more Harry Dworkin application
- Alexander, Gabriel N., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Alexander, Gabriel N., 1954-1967 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  Includes Board of Governors minutes 10/16/54; Review of status of Pending Applications for membership 9/29, 2p.
- Luskin, Bert L., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  Includes discussion material for an informal meeting at the home of Peter Kelliher
- Luskin, Bert L., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  Includes Applications for Membership - Tally Sheet 12/53 and related correspondence including opinions that membership standards should be more stringent; NAA Report of Committee on Legislation 5/23/53, 15p.
- Luskin, Bert L., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  Includes letter to G. Alexander summarizing discussion of regional membership meeting at Kelliner's house 10/1/54, 2p.
- Luskin, Bert L., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1954 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Luskin, Bert l., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Luskin, Bert l., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Luskin, Bert l., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Luskin, Bert L., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 52)